

Rhema Bassey

rhemabassey@gmail.com

Abeokuta, Ogun State, Nigeria Website:

https://www.coderbass.com/

Phone: +234 818 888 4151

Objective

I am a self taught full-stack web developer with a over a year experience. I currently work as a freelance web dev, helping individuals and small companies/businesses build their websites.

I use the MERN (MongoDB, Express, React, NodeJS) stack as a full-stack web developer, along with HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, etc. With these technologies, I can create a wide range of applications and websites tailored to your specifications and needs.

I have a passion for learning things and applying my knowledge to solve challenging tasks.

Programming Skills

- Languages: JavaScript, ES6, JQuery, HTML, CSS, Python
- Frameworks/Technology: Git, GitHub, React, Heroku, Bootstrap
- **Software**: Postman, VS Code, Chrome DevTools

Education

Physics-Electronics

Sept 2016 — August 2020

Babcock University

Bachelor of Science: Physics-Electronics Babcock University - Ilishan-Remo, Ogun.

Graduated with a 4.24/5 GPA (Second Class-Upper Honors).

Experience

Udemy

Sept 2020 — March

Full-Stack Web Development BootCamp

I completed a 55 total hour web development boot camp course on Udemy.

FRABEN Electrical Services

July 2021 — August 2021

Freelance Web Developer

I was hired to build a landing page for the company as a freelance web developer. This was also my first commercial project.

Website: https://www.frabenelectricalservices.com

Morlade Beauty Plug Oct 2021 — Nov 2021

Building a Shoppify Store

Created a Shopify eCommerce store for a client to establish a digital presence for them, and expand their reach.

Zummit Infolabs

Nov 2021 — Present

Machine Learning Intern

Started internship as a data and machine learning developer. Zummit Infolabs is a Bangalore based company that has catered to globally recognized clients and specialize in services related to Information Technology in addition to providing archetypal training to young aspirants.

Interests

Topics of Interest: Cryptocurrencies, Artificial Intelligence, Nuclear Energy, Space travel and Exploration, Science and Philosophy.